Sometimes the music can lift you higher than you’ve ever been.
Praise This is a music, romance, comedy film directed by Tina Gordon.
When aspiring musical superstar Sam is forced to join her cousin's struggling, underdog praise team in the lead-up to
a national championship competition, she sees an opportunity to finally make her dreams come true.
Sam, played by Chloe Bailey.
Jess, played by Anjelika Washington.
Aaron, played by Druski.
Melissa, played by Birgundi Baker.
KiKi, played by Jekalyn Carr.
T.Y. Way, played by Quavo.
Praise This is a 2023 American musical comedy romance film directed by Tina
Gordon and starring Chloe Bailey and Anjelika Washington.
The rebellious Sam, a young woman with dreams of being a superstar singer-songwriter, joins an underdog Atlanta
praise-team choir when sent to live there from LA, hoping to lead them into the national competition.
The film was released on April 7, 2023, by Peacock.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of gospel, church, singing
competition, gospel music, music.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.